How much can a man take...before he gives back?
Lock Up is a action, crime, drama film directed by John Flynn.
Frank Leone is nearing the end of his prison term for a relatively minor crime.
Just before he is paroled, however, Warden Drumgoole takes charge.
Drumgoole was assigned to a hell-hole prison after his administration was publicly humiliated by
Leone, and has now arrived on the scene to ensure that Leone never sees the light of day.
Frank Leone, played by Sylvester Stallone.
Warden Drumgoole, played by Donald Sutherland.
Captain Meissner, played by John Amos.
Chink Weber, played by Sonny Landham.
Dallas, played by Tom Sizemore.
Eclipse, played by Frank McRae.
Lock Up is a 1989 American prison action film directed by John Flynn, and starring
Sylvester Stallone, Donald Sutherland, John Amos and Tom Sizemore.
It was released in the United States on August 4, 1989.
Stallone later said it was "Not a film that was produced and performed with enough
maturity to really make a significant impact on the audience or my career.
And that's the truth".
The film explores themes of prison, self sacrifice,
jail guard, car mechanic, prison warden.
The tone is emotional and intense.